(Penny:)Sweetie, can I just be the girl tonight?
(Leonard:)Absolutely. You're the girl, I'm the guy.
(Leonard:)Watch your football game
while I make you a plate here.
(Amy:)Thank you.
I'll get it. Go sports! Heh.
Hello-Io-Io.
(Leonard:)I thought you were out
with Sheldon and Amy.
(Raj:)I was, but it's their anniversary,
and I didn't wanna be a third wheel...
...so I figured I'd hang out
with you and Penny on your date.
(Leonard:)It's not really a great time.
Penny and I have some things to talk about.
No we don't, come on in!
(Penny:)Sweet.
(Amy:)I can't believe
I shaved my stomach for this.
(Dimitri:)Hey, Froot Loops.
(Dimitri:)You got a phone call.
(Howard:)Who is it?
(Dimitri:)A woman who says she's your mother
but sounds like your father.